devbistro.com 2009-05-12

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use | Dev Bistro

## Privacy Policy

At devbistro.com, protecting your privacy is of utmost importance to us. Our goal is to provide a safe, secure and friendly user experience. Our best efforts are used to ensure your personal information is kept secure and in accordance with the terms outlined in this policy. 

Information collected on this website is used for internal business purposes only. We do not sell, trade, or provide your private data (including email addresses) to third parties. This information is only used to provide basic functionality such as maintaining ownerships of the postings so that they can subsequently be edited. You can visit the site, search for jobs and resumes, and apply for jobs without having to log in or enter any personal information. 

Creating an account here merely requires choosing a username/password combination. Your password gets encrypted before being stored in our database. One-way hash encryption algorithm is used to perform this encryption which means that nobody (including the Administrator of this site) has access to your sensitive information. You are not required to provide your email address during the registration process. If provided, it can be used to reset your password in case you forget one. 

The site utilizes session (temporary) cookies in order to provide access to the data retrieved from the database by different pages during your browser session. Such cookies only exist for the duration of your browser session. 

## Terms of Use

It is illegal to harvest email addresses and/or personal information of our users (whether it is done in a manual or an automated way) for any purpose other than a) contacting employers or job seekers to apply for positions advertised, or b) contacting job seekers to discuss available job opportunities. Although we use all reasonable means to protect all information collected here, Dev Bistro is not responsible for any improper use of this information that is beyond our reasonable control. If you suspect any misuse, please email us immediately. 

You are not allowed to republish any of the postings/information found on on this site without prior written approval from Dev Bistro.

By accessing, using or posting information to this site, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy outlined above. If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us
